hello brothers and sisters this is ey on
ey censored Supernatural Bible changes
on YouTube and today is the 9th of
January
2024 I'm going to go ahead and do
another book review this was a a small
book that was I just finished it's 5x
7.5x 6 so it's a small
book very relevant and I cover well the
name of the book as you can see is Bible
truth and the strong delusion lying
signs and wonders I provide over 200
scripture
verses that have been obviously changed
in scripture the changes are
self-evident and I'm going to go ahead
and share with you a little bit of what
it looks like inside so this is my
manuscript and I go in and I talk about
what they can expect to see in the book
I talk about what types of Bible changes
that we were witnessing in our our
Bibles specifically the King James Bible
but every Bible and every translation
and languages are changing and we've
been testifying of this for the past 7
and a half years on YouTube at least on
my
channels and I go on and I talk about
what's happening with our scriptures and
then I talk about the Bible verses that
warned us of this hour very
important and then I go into talking
about the Bible changes like this one
now I did
not say what was change in these verses
because they really should be
self-evident to anyone who has eyes to
see this is First Kings
17:21 and this is what it says
today and
he stretched himself upon the child
three times and Cried unto the Lord and
said oh Lord my God I pray thee let this
child's
Soul come into him
again this was
Elijah in the Old
Testament a grown
man probably Elder in years I don't
know laying on top of a
child full body
contact three
times have would
you have you ever read
this would you allow your pastor to come
and lay on top of your child three
times it's
bizarre extremely
bizarre another one is this verse from 1
Corinthians
12:17
if the whole body were an eye where were
the
hearing if the whole were hearing where
were the
smelling and if you can't discern how
weird this one is I don't know what to
tell
you Luke
19:27 this will be the last one I'll
show
you but those mine enemies which would
not that I should re over them bring
them hither and slay them before
me do you remember
that do you remember this
parable of Jesus saying
commanding that his enemies should be
murdered as mentioned the Spanish Bible
in this same verse says that Jesus said
to behead them to decapitate the
enemies
well this
contradicts love your
enemies
right think about it but these are the
types of changes we see throughout
scripture okay I'll show you one
more 1 John 1:6 if we say that we have
fellowship with him and walk in darkness
we lie and do not the truth do you
discern the change here there's missing
a
word do not the
truth it was do not practice the
truth I
believe but it certainly wasn't do not
the truth that's utter nonsense that's
not proper English do not what the
truth do you see this is a change so I
do not identify what the changes are
because I believe that the Holy Spirit
alone is our teacher and can quickly
identify what the problem is if you're
seeking truth okay the Bible says that
God would send the strong delusion
because they did not love the truth now
I believe these are lying signs and
wonders that we're seeing happen in
scripture and it's being done by the
Antichrist it's not God changing
scripture because there is a
filthiness in a language that's now been
inserted all the Hallmarks of the evil
one there is a stench of soul forness
now in the Bible and I believe it's the
Antichrist and he is taking his position
as God in the Bible and there currently
is a great falling away and people who
are denying the Bible's changing are
worshiping the Beast it's just that
simple as harrowing horrifying
unbelievable as it sounds there's no
doubt about it here's where you can buy
my book on Amazon it was just published
in December by Bible truth and the
strong delusion lying signs and wonders
this was the book they actually held for
a while so it wasn't published until
January but I had submitted it in
December so this book is a paperback $10
and a great resource to quickly show
people these weird new verses and
language that's invaded our Bibles and
again not everyone has eyes to see we
know
that but this little tool can be helpful
for sharing numerous scripture verses
that have been altered again we're
seeing punctuation errors grammar errors
nonsense verses new names new words
words erased copy and paste
jobs emoticons and on and on it goes in
our own Bibles these are lying signs and
wonders do you have eyes to see do you
want eyes to see pray and fast and seek
the
Lord and
ultimately you don't need me to share
the truth about what's happening in
scripture because a holy
spirit can show
[Music]
you it's that
simple come out of Babylon wake up Oh
Sleeper seek the truth with your whole
heart mind soul and strength it's the
most
important it's the most
important
act here on Earth today for any believer
is to seek the truth wholeheartedly
Jesus Christ is the word of God and the
word of God ures forever we do not
worship the Bible we worship Jesus
Christ in spirit and in truth and the
word of God endures forever his words
are Eternal the Bible itself is
not the Bible Bible is subject to the
elements of this world and it's not
going to heaven with
you you can throw your Bible in a fire
throw it in a pool have your dog eat
it it can be destroyed here on Earth and
that's what's happening
supernaturally but the word of the Lord
endures forever and the word of God
endures forever because the word of God
exists outside of the Bible the word of
God does not exist exist because the
Bible
exists do you understand he who has ears
let him hear seek the Lord while he may
be
found brothers and sisters be strong and
courageous do not fear or be dismayed
for the Lord your God is with you
wherever you go feel free to email me at
eort Gmail and let me know if you have
any questions I don't have all the
answers I surely don't and I don't have
100% memory but I know that what I'm
reading the Bible
today is not the language of my heavenly
father and I can say that
with 100%
conviction much love and blessings to
each of you in Jesus name